Call the government! Alert the media! Hide the cat! ALF's back!
Project: ALF is a comedy, family, science fiction film directed by Dick Lowry.
Six years ago, the lovable intergalactic fugitive Gordon Shumway, best known as ALF, was on his
way back to his new home when the Alien Task Force finally caught up with him.
Now, he is being studied at a top-secret military base where he finds allies who feel that
ALF's existence should be announced to the world to ensure his safety...
especially when they learn that the abrasive Colonel Milfoil
wants ALF, and all Alien Life-Forms, destroyed.
ALF (voice), played by Paul Fusco.
Dexter Moyers, played by Miguel Ferrer.
Capt. Rick Mullican, played by William O'Leary.
Maj. Melissa Hill, played by Jensen Daggett.
Colonel Gilbert Milfoil, played by Martin Sheen.
Motel Manager, played by Ray Walston.
The film explores themes of escape, alien
life-form, examination, soldier, scientist.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.